<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name=	"about_pageSHARE">share</string>
    <string name=	"about_page">Hello, a meeting ride a bike safely app. Our app has been developed based on the open source license to create a little bit safer cyclists culture targeted at Seoul cyclists have developed the app. The purpose of location-based audio guide services in the area of ​​5077 required its own analysis intersections care information and safe riding position. Help us make a better app with your interest and advise please :) a lot to share. - Helmet developers -	</string>
    <string name=	"about_pageHi"	>Introduce</string>
    <string name=	"about_pageHelp">Help</string>
    <string name=	"about_pageCS"	>Bicycle knowledge management</string>
    <string name=	"about_pageLicense">Open source licenses</string>
    <string name=	"about_pagePL"	>Public data authorship</string>
    <string name=	"about_pageAlert">Precautions</string>
    <string name=	"about_pageHow_gps">How does GPS measurements?</string>
    <string name=	"about_pageGPS">GPS measurements will be done through a GPS measuring device built into the smartphone. The higher the GPS sensitivity will increase battery usage. The ability to use the map, you can increase the battery consumption.	</string>
    <string name=	"about_pageHow_Direct">How does the pathfinding capabilities?	</string>
    <string name=	"about_pageDirect">Directions Run cocoa made to navigate the app works Directions for motorcycle. (Please use for reference!) Also, to go to the cacao installation screen when not installed in the Navi app.	</string>
    <string name=	"about_pageHow_Route">How does the path to saving function?	</string>
    <string name=	"about_pageRoute">Save route will be saved and you\'re done, click the Start and press the start button, Refresh. You can find information related to the travel path and travel maps.	</string>
    <string name=	"about_pageHow_Save">	How does the security service function?	</string>
    <string name=	"about_pageSave">Security Service is a feature that the sensor built into the smartphone to detect your fall, and the user is sent to the location registration number by SMS if there is no response for the user during a fall detection requires a response, and a certain amount of time.	</string>
    <string name=	"about_pageHow_TTS">How does the voice guidance feature?	</string>
    <string name=	"about_pageTTS">Voice guidance feature is available for speech synthesis technology (Text to Speech) TTS built into smart phones, there is wide support may differ depending on the smartphone model. If the voice guidance does not appear, please switch to the Google TTS engine in the setup window. If you still can not hear the voice, please re-run the app!</string>
    <string name=	"about_pageHow_Alert"	>What is the risk zone guidance Does it work?	</string>
    <string name=	"about_pageAlerts">Risk Information Services segment consists of GPS-aware devices embedded in smartphones, it will be executed when you press the start button. This feature can increase the battery usage. (You can not risk notifications work properly, sometimes due to positioning errors.) The basic speedometer display In measuring the speed and overspeed operation during travel at 30km over the speed the voice guidance and screen transitions It occurs guidance. In addition, the speed of clicking the touch screen is not possible and stop using volume up (raising voice) button when more than 20km to please unlock the screen.	</string>
    <string name=	"about_pageAJM">Team Helmet	</string>
    <string name=	"about_pageAJM_Alert"	>This app is an app developed to increase the safety of cycling of users. Avoiding excessive use an app, and I\'ll always ask a safe ride! :)	</string>
    <string name=	"about_pageWhere"	>authorship</string>
    <string name=	"about_pageWhere_is"	>Weather - OpenWeatherMap, Seoul \nintersections information - ITSstandard node-link system \npedestrian areas - Seoul public data place \nAccident-prone areas - Seoul open data place \nChild protection areas - public data portal</string>
    <string name=	"about_pageBike">Bike management so!	</string>
    <string name=	"about_pageBikeis">1. Check your bicycle tire. \n2. Check brake status. \n3. Check suspension fork bolts. \n4. Check lube oil condition of chain sprocket. \n5. Reinjected into the bearing grease. \nlastly, Clean your bicycle once a week. Thank you for your safe ride! :)</string>
</resources>